Hello, my physical therapist Yui Hatano
Please enlighten me, I am inconvenient to do housework
I can't take a bath myself.
Then I'll go in and help you
Then i start
Please
Do you want to undress first?
Yes
Please also below
Trouble you
I prepare
Do you want to take it off?
Yes
Wait a minute
How did you get hurt?
Twisted waist in a car accident
Can't do a lot of things
Just leave it to me today
I'm going to help you brush your body
Yes
It hurts, let me tell you
About to start
Will it hurt?
Won't
Is it comfortable?
Yes
Does this hurt?
Won't
It turns out that there is this kind of service
Hand to me
Sorry
Going to continue
Are you okay?
Yes
Does this hurt?
Won't
Is the water temperature okay?
Can
Let's go in
Yes
Take your time
Are you okay?
Yes
Sorry
Is the water temperature okay?
Can
Please relax
Is it comfortable?
Very comfortable
I can't wash it myself
You can tell me what you need
My body has been sticky, now I feel much more comfortable
And it's been a long time since I had sex recently
Then you must be uncomfortable
Yeah
How long hasn't done it?
Almost 3 weeks
Then you must be uncomfortable
I've been holding back very hard recently
If I can help, please say
Really okay?
Is there such a service?
Yes
Can I look at your body first?
Want to see it?
Then I work hard
Please watch
The nipples are hard
Do you feel it?
Yes
How is it?
Haven't seen it so close
Can be closer
Really?
Can you see it well?
Yes
Can you see clearly?
Very clear
Very comfortable to touch like this
See? Yes
Please continue to enjoy
So cool
Can you hear it wet?
Yes
Going
So excited
Are you having an orgasm?
I'm excited too
The meat stick is hard
Are you okay?
Is the meat stick cool?
Yes
So cool
Really?
Is it cool?
Yes
Cool?
You are very hard
You can shoot if you want
Almost shot
Ok
You shot
My waist doesn't hurt anymore
Really? Great
Don't hurt
Thank you
So, let's start treatment
We want to stimulate the patient to make his waist heal
First ask for him
Yes
How are you, patient?
My lower body hurts
Is it?
Can't you move below?
Yes
Don't you even get up below?
Can't be hard
It's okay
I'm not working anymore
Don't worry, leave it to me
Really?
You turn around first
Does it hurt here?
Yes
I'll give you a massage first
How is it?
Doesn't feel any pain, will it hurt?
Won't hurt
What are you doing and is this treatment useful?
You have to treat the patient's mind together
Yes
This treatment is useless at all
The patient said he couldn't get up
This way he will become unconfident
Then you can do whatever you want
Really
Yes
Really okay?
What do you want?
I wanna kiss
And it's a tongue kiss
Doctor, he wants a tongue kiss
I really want to kiss my tongue
No problem
Do you really want to do this?
Listen to what the patient says
I got it
Otherwise the patient won't get better
Kiss him quickly
Got it
Then sorry
Feel good
Do you still want it?
Is it like this?
I didn’t take a bath, please clean it with my tongue.
Clean it up?
Use your tongue?
I got it
That's it
So comfortable
Clothes off
Trouble you
About to start
Will it smell?
No, lick the nipples too
Here?
It hurts to say
Won't hurt
Suck hard
Hard?
Great
I'll help you suck here too
Touch down
Is this okay?
Touch directly
You help me take it off
Ok
You have to invest in
Got it
To satisfy the guests
Be careful
Need to take off underwear
Want to be licked all over?
Yes
Is it comfortable?
It hurts to say
Are you okay?
Cool?
Licking meat stick
Meat stick?
Lick it clean for you
Don't be shy
I will lick it cleanly
You keep licking
Yes
Awesome
What is your body shaking?
Tell the patient that the asshole is cool
My asshole is cool
Tell him what happened next?
Butthole being caressed
Butthole feels great
Really
What does the patient think?
Great
You can take a closer look
Is it really possible?
I'm going to lick
So shy
How is it?
Very comfortable
We must continue to treat patients
You can see different places
Take it off
I got it
Too sexy
Please enjoy
You can pinch it
So soft
Too shy
Too abnormal
Please squeeze as much as you like
How is it?
So excited to be licked
Let's lick it together
Press our heads hard
Is that so?
Is it delicious?
Some saliva
Lick your cunt to the patient
What to do
Not like this
I don't know how to do it
The patient's head is here
Am I lying down?
Please lie down and lick me
See clearly
See?
How can I just take care of myself
Twist yourself
So cool
So comfortable
Orgasm
Cool enough
Your job is to satisfy the patient as much as possible
Take care of the patient's feelings
Got it, is it okay to blow like this?
Blow two together
Yes
Patient please stand up
I want to keep blowing
Ok
Go deeper
Yes, lick it inside
So cool
Cool?
Cool
Then comes the final treatment
Ask the patient to lie down
Got it
Treat the patient well
To be inserted
Fully inserted
Well topped
Is it so cool?
Cool?
Cool
I also want to make your nipples cool
So cool
Please watch
Orgasm
I'm dying
So cool
So impressed
Orgasm
Go on orgasm
Change the patient
So cool
Harder
I'm so cool
Come on, push the cart while blowing the meat stick
Keep licking
Yes
Do you want to be inserted by this cock?
So cool
Can I stand up and push the cart?
Cool
The cunt is so comfortable
How is it?
The patient has recovered and worked hard
Can I get a cream?
Yes, please cream me
So cool
Going
Shot
So cool
Show me the pussy that I got fucked clearly
Cool
Great
Can I get a cream?
Creampie me
Shoot me more
I'm much better, thank you
Really?
I have to come for treatment next time
No problem
Great
You behaved well
Really?